**[HOOK]**
*"Can you spell ‘quincunx’ or ‘sesquipedalian’?
These were just two of the mind-bending words that stumped even the brightest young minds in this year’s National Spelling Bee.
But how do *Americans* stack up?
A new poll reveals the shocking truth—most can’t even spell the simplest finalists!"*
**[NEWS]**
A recent survey found that **only 30% of Americans** could correctly spell the 2024 National Spelling Bee champion’s word—**"sesquipedalian"** (meaning long-winded).
Even more struggled with **"quincunx"** (a star-shaped pattern), with just **15% getting it right**.
Experts say the decline in spelling proficiency isn’t just about bees—it’s tied to digital communication and shorter attention spans.
**[WRAP]**
*"Want to test your skills?
Try spelling these words yourself—and share your results!
Will you make the cut, or are you a spelling bee dropout?
Drop a comment below!"* 🎤✨